[{"question":" Which two sets of values are printed by this function and sub?","options":[{"text":"id=5 Age = 20 Weight= ID=6 Age = 25 Weight=130","correct":false},{"text":"id=5 Age = 20 Weight=0 ID=6 Age = 25 Weight=130","correct":false},{"text":"id=5 Age = 20 Weight=Null ID=6 Age = 25 Weight=130","correct":false},{"text":"id=5 Age = 20 ID=6 Age = 25 Weight=130","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nFunction GetVitals(ID As Long, Age As Long, ptional Weight As Long) As String\n    GetVitals=\"ID=\" & ID &\"Age=\" & Age & \"Weight=\" & Weight\nEnd Function\nSub ShowVitals()\n    Dim ID As Long, Age As Long,Weight as Long\n    Debug.Print GetVitals(ID:=5,Age:=20)\n    Debug.Print GetVitals(ID:=6,Age:=25,Weight:=130\nEnd Sub\n```"},{"question":" This code shows the first statement of CalledSub. Which calling statement will work properly?","options":[{"text":"call Calledsub \"smith\",26","correct":false},{"text":"calledsub (surname=\"smith\", Age = 26)","correct":false},{"text":"calledsub (Surname:=\"Smith\", Age:=26)","correct":false},{"text":"calledsub \"smith\", 26","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the principal difference between a class and an object?","options":[{"text":"There is no meaningful difference. The terms are used interchangeably.","correct":false},{"text":"A dass declares an object's properties. An object completes the declaration by defining events and methods.","correct":false},{"text":"An object is a template for a class.","correct":false},{"text":"A class describes the design of an object. An object is an instance of that design.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What value does the MsgBox statement display?","options":[{"text":"2","correct":false},{"text":"10","correct":false},{"text":"First arg","correct":true},{"text":"3.1416","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nSub MySub(VarA As Long, ParamArray VarB() As Variant)\nMsgBox VarB(0)\nEnd Sub\nSub ShowValue()\nCall MySub(10, \"First arg\", 2, 3.1416)\nEnd Sub\n```"},{"question":" What object is needed to put a userform module in a VBA project?","options":[{"text":"associated standard code module","correct":false},{"text":"UserForm","correct":false},{"text":"associated class module","correct":false},{"text":"userForm class","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the output?","options":[{"text":"3","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":false},{"text":"9","correct":false},{"text":"6","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nSub UseSum()\nDim TestArray() As Integer, Total As Integer\nReDim TestArray(1)\nTestArray(1) = 6\nReDim TestArray(2)\nTestArray(2) = 3\nTotal = WorksheetFunction.Sum(TestArray)\nEnd Sub\n```"},{"question":" The Driver subroutine is declared by Sub Driver (Y). Which statement results in a compile error?","options":[{"text":"Driver x","correct":false},{"text":"call Driver(x)","correct":false},{"text":"call Driver x","correct":false},{"text":"Driver (X)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have several variables to display on a user form, and there are too many variables to display at once. Which control best enables the user to see all the variables?","options":[{"text":"Frame","correct":false},{"text":"multipage","correct":false},{"text":"TabStrip","correct":false},{"text":"ListBox","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Below is a function named SquareIt. Which version of the subroutine named Area results in a compile error?","options":[{"text":"sub Area()","correct":false},{"text":"Sub Area()","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nDim Result As Long, Side\nSide = 5\nResult = SquareIt(Cint(Side))\nEnd Sub\n```"},{"question":". EmailAddress() is an array. It is declared by Dim EmailAddress(10) As String, and option Base 1 is in effect. How many rows and columns are in EmailAddress()?","options":[{"text":"10 rows and 10 columns","correct":false},{"text":"10 rows and 1 column","correct":false},{"text":"10 rows and 0 columns","correct":false},{"text":"1 row and 10 columns","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which cell is selected if you run this code?","options":[{"text":"F5","correct":false},{"text":"F3","correct":true},{"text":"B3","correct":false},{"text":"E3","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which variable name is valid in VBA?","options":[{"text":"\\_MyVar","correct":true},{"text":"My_Var","correct":false},{"text":"My-Var","correct":false},{"text":"1MyVar","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nUse the following rules when you name procedures, constants, variables, and arguments in a Visual Basic module:\nYou must use a letter as the first character.\nYou can't use a space, period (.), exclamation mark (!), or the characters @, &, $, # in the name.\nName can't exceed 255 characters in length.\n```"}]